treocentral.com 2007-06-22

# treocentral.com >> About

|   
---  
|  |   
  |  | 

** treocentral.com >> About   
**Privacy Policy**** TreoCentral is deeply committed to protecting the privacy of Internet users. Below is information outlining our continued support for the responsible management of consumer information. 

**Consumer Information  **

During the process of accessing TreoCentral, we do not collect any personally identifiable information about you such as name, address, phone number, or e-mail address. However, TreoCentral does obtain some types of non-personally identifiable information such as the Internet Service Provider you use to connect to the Internet, your browser type, or the type of computer operating system you use (Macintosh or Windows, for example). The information collected by TreoCentral is used to improve the site to fit our users needs. 

In some cases, you may voluntarily provide personal information, such in the case of creating an account on our bulletin board or entering a contest.

TreoCentral, as well as most sites on the Internet, use "cookies" to enhance your experience on the web.

If you do not want the benefit of cookies, there is a simple procedure to manually delete your cookies. Please consult your web browser's Help documentation for more information. 

**Opt Out Procedure  **  
If you would like to "opt out," that is, to prevent any data from being stored by TreoCentral, please send an email to [editor@TreoCentral.com](mailto:editor@TreoCentral.com) 

If you have any additional questions about TreoCentral's dedication to consumer privacy, please contact us at [editor@TreoCentral.com](mailto:editor@TreoCentral.com)

|   |   
---|---|---  

Copyright ©1999-2007 TreoCentral. All rights reserved : Terms of Use : Privacy Policy

TREO and TreoCentral are trademarks or registered trademarks of palm, Inc. in the United States and other countries;   
the TreoCentral mark and domain name are used under license from palm, Inc.   
The views expressed on this website are solely those of the proprietor, or   
contributors to the site, and do not necessarily reflect the views of palm, Inc.
